

CONTACT

- +91-9360914365
- ✓ kavipriyagd02@gmail.com
- Malleshwaram, Bangalore
- www.linkedin.com/in/kavipriya-40123531

EDUCATION

2004 - 2007 JIWAJI UNIVERSITY

• Bachelor of Computer Science

2003 - 2004 ONEZERO COMPUTERS

• Diploma in Multimedia

SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Indesign
- AdobePremier
- Adobe Dreamweaver
- Adobe After Effects
- Corel Draw
- Canva
- MS Office

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Tamil (Fluent)
- Telugu (Basics)
- Kannada (Basics)
- Malayalam (Basics)

KAVI PRIYA

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

PROFILE

A Senior Graphic Designer with 5+ years of experience, specializing in web, print, brand messaging and Digital marketing. I have a proven track record in leading successful design projects, implementing design systems, and increasing website traffic, customer satisfaction, and sales. Accustomed to performing in dead-line driven environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CGM MEDIA | SALEM

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER [Remote]

MAR 2021 - APR 2024

- Collaborate with clients, senior executives, copywriters, and marketers to define strategic direction for designs based on market indicators and brand identity.
- Manage and lead a design team to develop high-quality marketing materials for web development projects and re - branding, including graphic design, custom logos, and website design
- Established trusting relationships with designers, vendors, and key clients

HIBU INDIA PVT LTD | BENGALURU

DEC 2013 - MAR 2015

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- · Conceptualizing visuals based on requirements.
- Creating images and layouts by using Photoshop & Illustrator softwares.
- Analyze the voice over and adding appropriate images in the video and adding effects/transitions.
- Proof reading and reviewing deliverables and project processes and upload the final video in the server.

MARLEN INFOMEDIA | CHENNAI

JUN 2010 - NOV 2011

TEAM LEADER GRAPHIC DESIGER

- Lead the end-to-end design for individual projects along with other designers.
- Create design templates and visual graphics for collaterals like brochures, flyers, presentations, infographics, email campaigns, television events, social media posts and websites.
- Update and maintain internal databases of designs, websites and YouTube videos.
- Coordinate with clients and managing a marketing, design, and development team.

EXPERTISE

- Social Media
- Branding
- Digital Marketing
- Web Design
- SEO
- Management Skills

PORTFOLIO

BEHANCE

www.behance.net/kavipriya7

YOUTUBE

www.youtube.com/@Petslike

WEBSITE DESIGN

www.petslike.in
www.lauraspring.co.uk
www.preservecompany.com
www.avantiway.com
www.bietjhs.ac.in
www.sssautomation.net
www.uyirmeiseithigal.com

CYS MULTIMEDIA | CHENNAI

TECHNICAL INSTRUCTOR

AUG 2008 - MAY 2010

- Manage student projects and placements. Analyze what aspects of the current position need to be changed or improved.
- Prepare lesson plans, organize workshops, seminars and guest lecturers
- Advise best practices and optimizations throughout design projects.
- Provide coaching and corrective action as needed for student workers.

ARENA MULTIMEDIA | CHENNAI

FEB 2007 - JUN 2008

MULTIMEDIA FACULTY & LAB TEAM LEADER

- Instruct student proctors and facility users on system usage and recommends best practices in digital media production.
- Maintain classroom training, testing and certification of student proctors.
- Coordinate students in visual media labs and other designated spaces to minimize downtime and ensure usability of lab systems during open hours.
- Ensure classes/projects are completed in a timely manner with a quality results.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the information given above is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Yours Faithfully, S. Kavipriya